[{"answer": "Yeah, it's funny, I dunno", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Well, I don't know about", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah, how about her", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah, how about her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah, she's a package full of something", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hi, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Fine...  How are you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well! Well, it could be you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No, really", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, I know", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't...I dunno", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, is this a bit", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, what is the matter with her? Is she crazy?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Hey! What is wrong with you?", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No! Not part of the show! Booing and hissing are not part of the show! You boo puppets! You hiss villains in silent movies", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, I can take it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I don't know, I just don't", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Hey, man", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How can you call yourself a clown and not know who my friend is", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Is he a clown? What, are you kidding me!", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hey, man", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well, what is he", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hi Mom, how's everything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "The burgers should be ready in a minute", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Did you knock her over too, or just the kids", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Really? Her mother", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What did you go up there to heckle her for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, YEAH! You gave her a taste of medicine, alright", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah. Yeah, I am my friend. Then the mugger, he comes to, and he starts chokin' me! So I'm fightin' him off with one hand and I kept drivin' the bus with the other, y'know? Then I managed to open up the door, and I kicked him out the door with my foot, you know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fire.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well, people kept ringin' the bell", "qsentId": 32}]